A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, John D. Rockefeller, Sr., Series A FA310
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence - Lent, F. - Life (Box 16, Folder 122)
  Lent, Frederick, November 2, 1929. Elmira College appeal.Lent, Suzanne T. E., October 18, 1928. Dime.Leonard, Ethel V., December 31, 1928. Christmas gift.Leonard, Lavis A., 1921. Wants to write a biography.Lesher, Arthur L., (Mr. and Mrs.), November 1921. Wedding invitation.Leseur, Octave, January 1, 1930. Best wishes.Leverhulme, Lord, November - December 1920. Asks for John D. Rockefeller's health secrets, John D. Rockefeller's comment on health regime.Lewis, Ethel Liston L., (Mrs.), 1925; 1931 - 1933. Strong family, got some silver from 54th Street.Lewis, Laura R., (Mrs.), 1910 - 1921; 1925; 1928 - 1929. Pocantico neighbors, golf, visits.Lewis, Grace N. S., (Mrs.), May 1928. Personal appeal.Libby, Charles T., November 29, 1928. The 18th Amendment.Libert, Gaston, September 1921. John D. Rockefeller gets Legion of Honor, Commander decoration.Life, Susan T., 1919 - 1931. Owego, New York friend. Owego news. Charles L. LaMonte and family. Marriage of niece, Mrs. Ely.
- Correspondence - Lightbody - Lossing (Box 17, Folder 123)
  Lightbody, Thomas M., 1920; 1929. Visit.Lindars, Edith E., (Mrs.), 1926; 1931. Christmas wishes, wedding announcement.Lincoln Hospital & Home, April 18, 1922. Thanks for Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial gift.Lincoln Memorial University, January 1923. Dinner invitation.Lindabary, Lillie, August 14, 1925. Thanks for flowers.Lindbergh, Col. Charles A. and Mrs. Anne, 1931. Visits.Lindenberg, Carl F., May 27, 1927. Wants to fly the Pacific.Lingo, William B., November 29, 1930. Medical appeal.Lingren, A. H., and daughter Fannie, 1923 - 1927. Old Cleveland employee, John D. Rockefeller gifts.Lippert, Hilda, 1920; 1924; 1927 - 1930. Visit.Lippincott, Anne M., 1924; 1928 - 1930. Sends book.Little, Brown & Company, June 1928. Sends books: "Sunlit Days" "Optimists Good morning" "Optimists Good Night"Livers, John L., (Mr. and Mrs.), June 1925. Wedding announcement.Livezey, J. Franklin, (Mrs.), 1921. Sends snap shot.Livingston, Max, October 1930. Condolence.Livingston, Walter F., March - April 1930. Photographs.Lloyd, W. S., November 1, 1927. Visit.Lockhart, James H., November - December 1925. Visit, Pittsburgh oil man.Lockwood, Lene, (Mrs.), August 18, 1930. Birthday wishes.Lockwood, Mary C., 1923; 1929. Pocantico neighbor, sale of property.Logan, Mary F., 1919 - 1921; 1927. Church appeal.Lord, Harry, October 20, 1930. Banker. Park River, North Dakota, remembers William Avery Rockefeller (Dr. Livingston), sends clipping.Lors Day Alliance of the United States, April - May 1925. Appeal.Lossing, D. R., December 27, 1926. Remembers William Avery Rockefeller from Norwich, Ontario Canada.
- Correspondence - Lothman - Lyon, W. D. (Box 17, Folder 124)
  Lothman, Fred W., 1920 - 1926. Cleveland friend, best wishes, condolences.Lothrop, Arthur E., (Mr. and Mrs.), September 1931. Marriage announcement.Lott, Erskine H., (Mr. and Mrs.), January 1923. Wedding invitation.Lottman, George D., July 1921. Medical photographs.Lotz, John, 1917 - 1921; 1927. Head of Alta House in Cleveland; John D. Rockefeller comments on personal aid to sick employee. Objects to parental relationship. Assistance., Jr. letter's to John D Rockefeller re: Lotz.Loucks, W. E., October 1, 1930. Personal appeal.Love, John, May 30, 1930. Church appeal.Love, Luciana B., (Mrs. Elmer D.), 1921; 1928. Visit.Love, Theresia K., (Mrs.), February 1929. Invitation.Lowdon, Elsie M., June 1925. Paintings for sale.Lowell, William, 1922 - 1931. Golf tees.Ludwig, Emil, February 1928. To meet John D. Rockefeller, (Junior letter to Senior).Ludwig, W. W., 1921. John D. Rockefeller. Gift for good sermon.Luhrs, Henry E., June - July 1931. Sends poem.Lyford, Oliver S., July 19, 1926. Remembers childhood visit.Lynch, Patrick, 1922 - 1929. Old Cleveland employee, sends flowers.Lyon, John, March 1923. Condolence.Lyon, William D., June - July 1929. Written a book on old age.
- Correspondence - M. Annunciata - Magee (Box 17, Folder 125)
  M. Annunciata, Sister, July 26, 1921. Appeal for Day Nursery.Mabon, Arthur F., (Mr. and Mrs.), July 1920. Birthday wishes.MacArthur, Pauline A.., February 1, 1922. Thanks for oratorio.MacArthur, R. S., 1922 - 1923. Church appeal, condolence.MacColl, Alexander, July 11, 1928. Birthday wishes, Briarcliff minister.MacCracken, Henry, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1919 - 1920; 1924 - 1926. Vassar College activities.MacFadden, Minnie A., August 19, 1929. Gift.MacGowan, Frances, July 24, 1929. Visit.MacLeish, Andrew, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1919 - 1920; 1929. Denominational giving.MacNeal, Frederic A., 1929 - 1931. Visits.MacVicar, Agnes M., (Mrs.), 1929 - 1932. Pocantico Hills, gifts.Macy, V. Everit, and daughter Edytha, 1921; 1930. Visits, condolence, gifts.Madlin, Emily, September 1919. Loan.Magee, Mary, 1919 - 1930. Personal gifts to golfing partner. One of John D Rockefeller's dimes to her sister, a nun.
- Correspondence - Mai - Marston (Box 17, Folder 126)
  Mai, Emma, April 17, 1926. Visit.Makarius, Cordelia B., 1928 - 1931. Visit, magazine article.Malin, Ida E., (Mrs.), January 1929. Remembers John D. Rockefeller's gift to Ohio minister.Malone, Alice, (Mrs.), January 16, 1928. Christmas gift.Maloney, Martin, January - February 1927. Visit.Manbeck, C. B., February - March 1931. Photograph.Manhattan Navy Club, August - September 1919. Appeal.Nanning, William T., October 1928. Best wishes, Prohibition sermon.Margot, Bertha, 1920 - 1923. John D. Rockefeller sold her Standard Oil stock.Marie Dolores, Sister, 1920; 1922. Appeal for aid.Mark Twain Society, November 1927. Invitation to be honorary V. P.Markham, Henry F., April 1923. Personal appeal.Marriner, B. H., August 21, 1923. Condolence.Marriner, Mary, (Mrs.), 1926 - 1927. Personal gift.Marsh, Catherine, Mary, 1925. Wedding gift.Marsh, Daniel L., April - June 1930. Sends book.Marsh, Harriet H., August 1923. Wedding gift.Marsh, Helen E., February 4, 1927. Personal appeal.Marsh, Joseph W., (Mr. & Mrs.), June 1928. Wedding announcement.Marston, Hunter S. & Edgar, 1925 - 1930. Dimes. Visits. Wishes.
- Correspondence - Martin, E. A. - Maxwell (Box 17, Folder 127)
  Martin, Edward A., 1924 - 1931. Best wishes, gifts.Martin, W. H., July 27, 1925. Amusing story.Martin, William H., 1929. Greetings.Marx, Nathan, 1930. Golden Wedding anniversary wishes.Mary Emmanuel, Mother, 1927 - 1931. Dime appeal for convent, (sisters of Mary Magee).Marymount College, 1924. Appeals.Mason, Miss C. E., 1920 - 1931. Appeals for Tarrytown school.Mason, Charles B., Jr., August 1926. Wedding gift.Mason, Dorothy P., June 1923. Wedding gift.Mason, Florence M. (Mrs.), July 8, 1929. Birthday greetings, autograph sought on postcard of boyhood home.Mason, M. C, January 21, 1928. India school appeal.Mason, Walter C., (Mrs.), August - September 1922. Condolence.Masonic Lodge, Tarrytown, December 22, 1919. John D. Rockefeller gift.Mastick, Seabury C., July - August 1926. Golf.Mather, Samuel L., (Mrs.), 1927; 1931. Girls' school, condolence.Matteson, George H., February 24, 1928. Information about William P. Cowan.Matthews, Jennie L., (Mrs.), May 9, 1921. Church appeal.Matthieson, C. H., July 1922. Personal appeal.Maxwell, Joseph K., (Mrs.), February 26, 1931. Information on communism.
- Correspondence - McAlpin - McCall (Box 17, Folder 128)
  McAlpin, Dr. and Mrs. Hunter and Family, 1920 - 1931. William Rockefeller's daughter. Wedding gifts to children. Visits. Description of John D. Rockefeller's 1929 statement and its impact on the stock market.McAcoy, John V., February 28, 1928. Personal appeal.McCall, Lenore, 1922. Wedding gifts.
- Correspondence - McCampbell, Sally (Mrs.), 1920-1927 (Box 17, Folder 129)
  New Jersey farmer. Visits. Gifts.
- Correspondence - McCampbell, Sally (Mrs.), 1928-1933 (Box 18, Folder 130)
- Correspondence - McCarthy, E. - McNally (Box 18, Folder 131)
  McCarthy, Edward, 1920. Autograph picture to "look alike."McCarthy, Mary, (Mrs.), June 17, 1921. Personal appeal.McCesney, H. G., March 1931. Card.McClave, Charlotte D., (Mrs.), 1926 - 1927. Help in securing compensation from railroad.McConnell, Lucy H., February 4, 1931. Photograph.McCook, Harriet, 1920. Wedding gift.McCord, Joseph A., 1927 - 1930. Visits.McCormick, Cyrus, 1921; 1929 - 1931. Condolences, tributes.McCrea, Ruth C., September 1925. Wedding gift.McDonald, John C., (Mrs.), May 1928. Condolence.McEvilly, Martin J., November 1928. Photographs.McEvitt, William, June 1926. Wants to lead band at birthday celebrations.McFarlane, J. H., February 1928. Sends book.McGarnn, Marion D., (Mrs.), 1927 - 1928. Gifts, condolences, memories of Forest Hill.McGiffert, Katharine W., 1920 - 1921. Wedding present.McGinnig, R. M., August - September 1931. Best wishes.McGoff, Mary, (Mrs.), 1925 - 1927. New York employee.McGrath, J. M., 1928. Regarding Bishops appeal.McGregor, Rose, January 2, 1931. Best wishes.McIntosh, Henry P., August - September 1922. Visit.McKay, J. A., October 1923. Sends publications.McKay, S. L., February 25, 1930. Sends snapshot.McKay, Virginia O., (Mrs.), (Robert G.), September 1925. Personal appeal.McKeogh, Arthur, 1929 - 1931. Writer, wants information.McKeown, A. R., (Mrs.), March 20, 1931. Thanks for card.McKinlock, George, (Mrs.), 1923 - 1928. Visits.McKown, Alice M., (Mrs. J. Boyd), 1924; 1930 - 1931. Appeal, cards, wishes.McLauchlan, Jay C., (Mr. & Mrs.), September 1925. Wedding invitation.McLeon, Pauline, (Mrs.), July 20, 1928. Church appeal.McLain, Albert O., March 14, 1930. Tribute.McMillan, Leighton G., (Mr. & Mrs.), 1906; 1925 - 1929. Personal appeal.McMurray, Welburn G., May 1931. Chinese education.McNally, James C., July - August 1928. Dimes, article in British-American magazine.
- Correspondence - Mead - Mills, A. W. (Box 18, Folder 132)
  Mead, Elsie C., (Mrs. Robert G.), January 1925. Surprise party for Junior.Meadows, George W., March 8, 1929. Saw picture in the paper.Meagher, Winifred, (Mrs. John), July 1930. Birthday wishes.Meinhardi, Dr. E. J., 1920 - 1923. John D. Rockefeller gave chiropractor endorsement.Mellen, Nellie F., October 30, 1922. Church appeal.Mellow, Dr., December 1929. Condolence.Melone, Harry R., April 1929. Request photographs.Merchants Bank & Trust Company, Daytona Beach, Florida, July - August 1929. John D. Rockefeller's interest in banking problems as bank closes.Mertz, Marie S., August 3, 1930. Received photograph.Merrick, Eliza J., February - March 1930. Huron Street Hospital.Merrill, Charles E., Jr., (Mr. and Mrs.), February 1926. Wedding invitation.Merrill, Isaac L., August - November 1927. Golf visits.Merritt, Hulett C., 1922 - 1928. Friendly sentiments from one of the Merritts.Mertz, Eva, April 29, 1929. Received Rockefeller dime.Merville, Ernest E., 1928 - 1929. Memories of old commercial school which John D. Rockefeller attended.Metcalf, James A., February 1929. Personal loan refused.Metropolitan Museum of Art, July 1923. Permission to photograph Sargent portrait.Michael, Nathan L., April 9, 1924. Thanks for dime.Miers, Elijah, (Mrs.), July 7, 1922. Birthday wishes.Miers, Evelyn, 1931. New Years and birthday greetings.Milburn, John G., August 13, 1930. Condolence.Miles, Grace C., (Mrs. J. S.), April 29, 1927. "People who Raised You" - advertisement.Miller, Charles, 1922; 1927; 1928. Described operation of Galena Oil Company and why he left. John D. Rockefeller's comments on business methods.Miller, Ellen R., (Mrs. E. E.), April 11, 1920. Appeal.Miller, Emmett L., (Mrs.), July 16, 1931. Birthday wishes.Miller, Hattie, (Mrs. F. E.), September 25, 1922. About old Standard Oil employer.Miller, Hugh G., April - May 1929. Sends book.Miller, Joseph C., June 1924. Wedding invitation.Miller, Martin C., July 1931. Request autograph.Miller, Morris, March 9, 1931. Introducing midgets.Miller, Roman J., June 1925. John D. Rockefeller's visit to Lakehurst; remembers previous meeting.Miller, W. A., August 8, 1927. Visit.Miller, Wesley C., July 17, 1931. Sends golfing device.Miller, Zella B., July 14, 1930. Birthday wishes.Milligan, Harold V., 1921 - 1929. Organist, 5th Avenue Baptist Church, gifts.Milliken, Dudley, 1919 - 1924. Visits, condolence.Mills, Anna, June 8, 1925. Appeal for home for the aged.Mills, Arthur W., 1929 - 1931. Congratulations on Stewart fight.
- Correspondence - Mills, C. M. - Moeller, H. (Box 18, Folder 133)
  Mills, C. M., November 1929. Regarding J. T. Sencabaugh, Standard Oil employee, sends dimes.Mills, William S., January 1923. Sends book.Milton, David M., (Mrs.), 1926; 1930 - 1931. Wedding gift to daughter, (Abby's first mother -in-law), hope for grandchildren.Miner, Kathlyn, February 1927. Sends photo of John D. Rockefeller.Minnerly, Emma A., 1920 - 1931. Housekeeper. Household news. New Job. Gifts.Mitchell, Florence, (Mrs. W. S.), 1921 - 1931. Widow of counsel. Gifts. Advice. Visits.Mitchell, Jessie S., June 1919. Gift.Moeller, Dr. Henry, 1921 - 1924. Visits, Did lab work for John D. Rockefeller, dimes, John D. Rockefeller's diet, condolence.
- Correspondence - Moeller, H. N. - Motts (Box 18, Folder 134)
  Moeller, Dr. Henry N., (son), 1925; 1929. Visit, photograph.Moffett, A., October 1920. Record of tank steamer "John D. Rockefeller."Moffett, James A., Jr., November 1, 1923. Condolence.Moghabghab, Faddoul, 1922 - 1923. Gifts.Mohr, George W., June - July 1926. Sends copy of letter to John D. Rockefeller, Jr.Moncho, Antonio A., May 9, 1929. Sends raisins.Monnette, Orra, February - March 1921. Request for autograph.Montague, Gilbert H., July 29, 1929. Why he wrote on Standard Oil Company, Toussig at Harvard suggested it.Montague, H., 1928 - 1929. Tribute to John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr.Monterey Chamber of Commerce, August 1920. Sends dime.Montgomery, Dudleigh E., October 1926. Wedding announcement.Moore, David, January 1928. Dime.Moore, Elsie L., (Mrs. Jared S.), March 4, 1924. Church appeal.Moore, Harry S., April - May 1920. Condolence.Moore, Mabel, 1925 - 1928. Visits.Moore, Margaret E., April - May 1923. Visits.Moore, Paul, August 1927. His father's experiences.Moran, Irene H., March 1925. (Mrs.), Dimes for her children, individual note from each.Moravia Fire Department, July 1922. Wants John D. Rockefeller to buy department a fire engine.Morehouse, C. L., (Mrs.), July - September 1922. Attack on Standard Oil; John D. Rockefeller points out inaccuracies.Morehouse College, March 1, 1927. Glee Club would sing for John D. Rockefeller.Morgan, Annie, (Mrs.), April - May 1923. Best wishes.Morgan, J. P., August 31, 1925. Thanks for condolences.Morgan, Marian B., (Mrs.), January 1931. Memories of Mrs. L. S. Rockefeller.Morgan, Reed A., (Mr. & Mrs.), June 1929. Receiving 1922 wedding invitation.Morgan, William J., September 1929. Account of John D. Rockefeller's purchases of first car (1898?).Morrell, Clara, 1920 - 1923. Gifts.Morrell, W. B., October 20, 1929. Dime.Morris, John S., (Mr. & Mrs.), June 1926. Gift to Cleveland church.Morris, Stuyvesant, Jr., November 1926. Wedding invitation.Morrison, S. H., January - February 1930. Sends watch.Morrow, Dwight W., (Mr. & Mrs.), 1931. Condolence, (also note from daughter Ann M. Lindleigh).Morse, Marion V., (Mrs. Harry F.), January 26, 1930. Visit.Moss, Charles H., May 1928. Remembers visit at the Laurel-in-the-Pines.Motts, Howard E., July 1926. Wants to use golf course at Forest Hill.
- Correspondence - Mouat - Murphy, D. T. (Box 18, Folder 135)
  Mouat, Thomas G., 1919 - 1923. Heating contractor.Moulds, John F. July - August 1929. University of Chicago chapel.Mount Holyoke College, November 1925. Invitation.Muchmore, Henry E., April 9, 1929. Sends poem.Mueller, October, 1930. Marriage announcement.Muller, Wilhelmina, May - June 1920. Wedding gift.Mullins, Isla M., (Mrs.), October - November 1930. Sends biography of E. Y. Mullins.Munn, Margaret L., September 1930. Sent poem to John D. Rockefeller, wants it back.Murdock, James O., October 6, 1925. University of Chicago alumni meeting.Murphy, C. V., August 1921. Wants evergreen trees.Murphy, D. T., August 1931. Claims to have saved John D. Rockefeller's life on Duluth, Messabi & Northern Railway by preventing a crash.
- Correspondence - Murphy, Julia B. (Mrs.), 1920-1922 (Box 18, Folder 136)
  Starr J. Murphy's widow. Gifts to family. John D. Rockefeller policy on caring for employees' widows. Personal relations. Correspondence with Murphy children.
- Correspondence - Murphy, Julia B. (Mrs.), 1923-1927 (Box 19, Folder 137)
- Correspondence - Murphy, Julia B. (Mrs.), 1928-1931 (Box 19, Folder 138)
- Correspondence - Murray, D. - Myers, C. (Box 19, Folder 139)
  Murray, Donald, November 3, 1927. Thanks for map.Murray, Evelyn S., (Mrs.), 1928 - 1919. Personal appeal.Murray, George, (Mr. and Mrs.), 1925 - 1926; 1929 - 1931. Best wishes, visits.Mustikhan, Shahjehan, October 15, 1930. Personal appeal.Myers, Cortland, June 1926. Visit.
- Correspondence - Myers, Dr. Johnston, 1919-1923 (Box 19, Folder 140)
  Chicago minister, Immanuel Baptist Church. Gifts. Myers's work with the poor.
- Correspondence - Myers, Dr. Johnston, 1924-1931 (Box 19, Folder 141)
- Correspondence - Myers, S. B. - Myrick (Box 19, Folder 142)
  Myers, Sigo, (Mr. and Mrs.), April 5, 1931. Visit.Myrick, Lily K., July 22, 1931. Personal appeal.
- Correspondence - Naef - Niles, S. H. (Box 19, Folder 143)
  Naef, Josephine, (Mrs.), December 30, 1930. Gift.Nanna, B., March 1929. Sends book on businessmen.Nash, Anna R., 1931 - 1932. Frank Rockefeller's daughter, gifts.Nash, William A., March 1927. Frank Rockefeller's son-in-law.National Child Labor Committee, 1919 - 1922. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Navy Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), Norfolk, Virginia, 1924; 1929. Anniversary celebration.Nelson, Edwin J., 1920; 1929. Lakewood educator, John D. Rockefeller gifts.Nelson, J. Homer, 1920 - 1924. Minister at Pocantico Hills and Maine, joy in work.Nelson, Ted, January 30, 1930. Dime.Nethken, H. W., July 27, 1927. Dividend policy of Atlantic Refining.New Jersey Baptist Convention, 1919 - 1920. John D. Rockefeller gifts.New York Child Labor Committee, 1919 - 1922. John D. Rockefeller gifts.New York Homeopathic College, 1923 - 1927. Medical appeals, John D. Rockefeller quoted as being a homeopathist.New York State Baptist Convention, July 1921. Rockefeller gifts.New York Tax Reform Association, 1920 - 1922. John D. Rockefeller gifts.Newman, Charles C., June 1921. Repair work at Lakewood.Newport Training School, April 9, 1925. School appeal.Newton, Mildred G., (Mrs.), October 1926. Marriage announcement.Nibley, C. W., December 1924. Mormon bishop. Thanks for good works.Nicholson, Thomas E., August 1929. Visit.Nichols, S. A., (Mrs.), December 10, 1926. Claims relationship.Nicholson, Louise, H., (Mrs.), August 27, 1930. Wondered if Sr. making restitution for damages done by Standard Oil to father J. E. Hall.Nielsen, H. B., n.d., Describes John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller Jr., Abby Aldrich Rockefeller and boys attending church in Pocantico Hills.Niles, Robert L., (Mrs.), March 20, 1923. Sends book.Niles, S. H., July 1920. Visit.
- Correspondence - Nightingale, Emma B. (Mrs.), 1921-1931 (Box 19, Folder 144)
  Cortland, New York, cousin. John D. Rockefeller gifts to her and her brother, Edward Boice. Problems of old age. Gifts to other family member, and her nephew Eli Brusie.
- Correspondence - Niven - Nyholm (Box 19, Folder 145)
  Niven, R. E., December 1931. Memories of A. Judson.Nolan, L. E., April 1929. Poem.Nolting, E. L., March 1928. Sends photos of Florida visit.Nomburg, Mack, April 1926. Has Stone Mountain half dollars to distribute.Norris, J. Frank, April 1923. Wants interview.Northrop, Frank, 1921; 1926. Advice on continuing the use of oxygen.Norton, Emma L., 1919 - 1920. John D. Rockefeller gifts, condolence.Norton, Elliot S., January 3, 1930. Golf invitation.Noyes, Marion W., February - March 1925. Sends picture.Nutt, Alice E., 1918 - 1931. Old Cleveland friend. Gifts. Remembers church activities.Nuveen, John, June 1929. Church appeal.Nyholm, Thorwald, 1928 - 1929. Christmas greetings.
- Correspondence - Oberlin College - Oglebay (Box 19, Folder 146)
  Oberlin College, October 1927. Inauguration invitation.Oborn, J. Wesley, August 1929. Barber named Lancaster recollects John D. Rockefeller.O'Brien, Charles V., February - March 1922. Sends picture.O'Brien, James, (Mrs.), July 22, 1927. Visit.Ocean County Boy Scouts, 1927. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Ocean County Council of Religious Education, 1925 - 1929. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Ocean County Health Association, May 1927. Appeal.Ocean County Sunday School Association, 1924. John D. Rockefeller contribution.Odell, Wallace, March - April 1925. Tarrytown library.O'Donnell, Annie, (Mrs.), July 30, 1931. Sends fairy story.Oehm, Elleanor, 1930. Dime photo.Oetling, Millie, March 1930. Personal appeal.Oglebay, Earl W., June 1922. Marriage announcement.
- Correspondence - O'Hara, Mary Van Duyne, 1919-1924 (Box 20, Folder 147)
  Mrs. John O'Hara. Moravia cousin. Gifts to her and to family members through her.
- Correspondence - O'Hara, Mary Van Duyne, 1925-1931 (Box 20, Folder 148)
- Correspondence - Ohio Society of New York - Osborn, H. F. (Mrs.) (Box 20, Folder 149)
  Ohio Society of New York, 1929 - 1931. MeetingsOler, Wesley M., 1920 - 1927. President, American Ice Company, Refrigeration, Personal friendship.Olmsted, Mabelle, (Mrs.), November 1920. Thanksgiving at "Pine Lodge" with John and Laurance in attendance.Olmsted, Maud L., May 1925. Visit, condolence.Ormond Chamber of Commerce, 1927. Invitation to join.Ormond Hotel, 1929 - 1931. Welcome, invitation.Ormond Union Church, 1927 - 1929. John D. Rockefeller contributions.Orr, Robert P., 1927; 1928. Sends archery outfit.Orton, Bella, March 24, 1924. Dime.Osborn, Catherine A., (A. T.., Mrs.), 1920 - 1922; 1927. Greeting.Osborn, Henry Fairfield, (Mrs.), 1925 - 1927. Sargent portrait copies, J. S. Sargent's comments on painting John D. Rockefeller's portrait.
- Correspondence - Osborne, Laura H. (Mrs.) - Owen, Marie B. (Mrs.) (Box 20, Folder 150)
  Osborne, Laura H., (Mrs.), May 27, 1926. Visit.Oscher, Bernice S., (Mrs.), July 16, 1927. Dimes.Oser, (Mrs. Max), September 1931. Mathilde McCormick OSER, Visit, (granddaughter).Owego Baptist Church, August 10, 1931. Appeal.Owego Free Academy, April - June 1927. John D. Rockefeller's old school.Owen, George D., 1928 - 1931. Ormond minister, visits.Owen, Marie B., (Mrs.), January 1929. Sends book.
- Correspondence - Pack - Patteson (Box 20, Folder 151)